[
    {
        "Question": "Who is prime minster of india",
        "Answer": "Narendra Modi",
        "Option": [
            "Narendra Modi",
            "Sir Keir Starmer",
            "Sebastien Lecornu",
            "Mikhail Mishustin"
        ]
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is a capital of india",
        "Answer": "New Delhi",
        "Option": [
            "New Delhi",
            "Maharashtra ",
            "Lucknow",
            "Patna"
        ]
    },
    {
        "Question": "what is a largest animal in our world",
        "Answer": "Blue whale",
        "Option": [
            "Blue whale",
            "Tiger",
            "Lion",
            "Kit"
        ]
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is a best language in programing",
        "Answer": "Java",
        "Option": [
            "python",
            "Java",
            "Node Js",
            "ASP.Net"
        ]
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is a capital of france",
        "Answer": "Paris",
        "Option": [
            "Paris",
            "Canberra",
            "Ottawa",
            "Brasillia"
        ]
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which is a largest country in the world",
        "Answer": "Russia",
        "Option": [
            "Russia",
            "China",
            "America",
            "India"
        ]
    },
    {
        "Question": "which is the best online shoping platfrom",
        "Answer": "Amazon",
        "Option": [
            "Amazon",
            "Flipkart",
            "Myntra",
            "Shopsy"
        ]
    },
    {
        "Question": "Who is the prime minster of America",
        "Answer": "Donald Trump",
        "Option": [
            "Donald Trump",
            "Narendra Modi",
            "Sir Keir Starmer",
            "Mikhail Mishustin"
        ]
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the full form of ATM",
        "Answer": "Automated Teller Machine",
        "Option": [
            "Automated Teller Machine",
            "Bank of Baroda",
            "Unified Payments Interface",
            "Portable Document Format"
        ]
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the full from  of PDF",
        "Answer": "Portable Document Format",
        "Option": [
            "Portable Document Format",
            "Unifrom resource locator",
            "eXtensible Markup Language",
            "Scalable Vector Graphics"
        ]
    }
]